Lukin Maksim, Software Engineer, http://lukin.io

Feb 19, 1990, Eastern Europe, Married

Experience:

Senior Ruby on Rails developer at Mobilunity (Nov 2019 – current)

Working as Senior Engineer using Ruby on Rails, consulting client, developing new features, optimizing existing code, resolving bugs.

— Senior Ruby on Rails developer at Aejis (2018 – Aug 2019, ~2y)

Ruby (and Rails), sometimes NodeJS/React for outsourcing company, designing API.

— Senior Ruby/JS Engineer, Team Lead/PM at Facewatch (2013 – 2018, 5y)

Backend development using Ruby and Sinatra. Small services based on Ruby on Rails. API based on service oriented architecture, Amazon services. Frontend based on BackboneJS. Integration with Metropolitan Police (London), Facial recognition using external API. Security Audit/PenTests. Writing RSpec tests and documentation. Implement new API.

— iOS Engineer at <u>jaccomo</u>, <u>EVENTAGRATE</u> (2012 – 2013, 1y)

Developing corporate applications for iPad, bluetooth messenger for conferences. Porting from Java/Swing application to iOS application. Development of jPass application.

— Ruby on Rails developer at <u>GAP Intelligence</u> (2009 – 2011, 2y)

Backend/Frontend development of DataCenter v2. DevOps tasks.

— **DevOps** at **MFS-Service** (2008 – 2009, 1y)

Administration of network of 100 workstations, delivering server reliability, some PHP.

Summary:

Writing clean, SOLID code. Tests, automated tests, CI/CD, Amazon services.

Experience in development with Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, API, Redis, Sidekiq

Understanding Frontend-related side, HTML/CSS, JS (TypeScript, ReactJS, Redux, Backbone.js);

DevOps basic skills (Linux, Chef/Ansible, Docker);

Had experience in iOS development, NodeJS;

Agile/Scrum, TDD/BDD;

Education:

Hardware Engineering faculty (Professional College of Computer Science, 2003-2006);

Interests:

Interested in Python, GO (or TypeScript, Hardware (IoT));

Learning new technologies, self-development. Traveling, running, swimming, biking.

Contacts:

Mobile: +38 (063) 765-49-17 Email: lukin.maksim@gmail.com

Skype: lukin.maksim

Github: https://github.com/sesharim **Linkedin**: http://linkedin.com/in/sesharim